David M. Lin

Frisco, TX 75034 • 972.591.1709 • dave.go.swim@gmail.com • www.OneStreamline.com

Objective

Seeking an opportinuty to chat with your orginazation about interesting things happening.

Summary

Yogi, gardener, and software engineer. I work for a software and healthcare company who makes it easy for people to make educated choices about their health care options.

With a strong ability to research and solve complex issues independently, I am a self-motivated individual who learns new technologies quickly.

Currently working on microservice projects using Clojure and Java with test frameworks; cucumber by Ruby and Gatling in scala.

Experience

Always-intermediate Software Engineer (Journeyman) HSQ1 (acquired Prism in January 2014) July 2012 - Present Frisco, TX, and Portland, OR

- CI/CD
- Clojure... Datomic, docker,
- Java... microservice, AWS, docker,
- Work in progress for External APIs: Apigee Edge, JavaScript, Groovy, JMeter.
- Work in progress for Geocoding service: Microservice, Java, Sprint Boot, DynamoDB, Cucumber.
- Work completed on the Admin Console v1: Java, Spring, Oracle SQL Developer.
- Work completed on the PatSat project: Google Analytics, Java, JSP, JavaScript.
- Work completed on Clarus (C3): C#, ASP.NET, JavaScript, SQL, LINQ.
- Project management software mastered: JIRA, Team Foundation Server.
- Search speed enhanced: Solr, Asynchronous operations, In-Memory caching, Stored Procedure optimization.
- Web applications developed with the Model-View-Controller (MVC) architectural pattern.
- SSO (Single Sign-On) security implementation: Security Assertion Markup Language (SAML).
- Website issues resolved with various tracing and logging technologies: ELMAH, MiniProfiler, Firebug, SAML tracer, SoapUI, dotMemory, Apigee trace tool.

1 of 2 4/12/20, 9:26 PM

Interactive Web Developer An Interactive Agency in Dallas

November 2008 - June 2012 Dallas, TX

- Met with clients to discuss their software needs and provide solutions to integrate our website into their IT operations. An interactive web developer/BA role.
- I'm updating this section to generalize what I learned from this job. But all the technologies here are either outdated or I simply don't remember them.
- Simply put, I did C#, ASP.NET, and SQL stuff

Web Developer Amensys Inc.

May 2007 - November 2008 Plano, TX

- At Amensys, we developed an internal management application that is an intranet web-based application.
- Created presentation layer and developed the user controls and custom controls.
- Applied Microsoft Enterprise Library's data access application block in data access layer.

Technical Skills

- Java, Spring framework
- HTTP
- Clojure, lein
- AWS: CloudWatch.
- SNS, SQS,
- Lambda,
- Elastic Search
- Cucumber, Ruby
- Visual Studio Code
- Gatling, Scala
- Python

- DynamoDB
- Datomic
- Apigee Edge
- APIs
- RESTful Web Services
- Microservices
- cURL
- Postman

- DynamoDB
- Datomic
- Apigee Edge
- APIs
- RESTful Web Services
- Microservices
- cURL
- Postman

Technical Skills (my path)

- Firebug (my fav)
- C#
- SQLLINO

- Groovy
- Tomcat
- JMeter Load Testing
- .NET Framework
- IIS IIS
- JavaScript
- AngularJS
- JavaScript
- AngularJS

Education

Master of Science in Electrical Engineering; Specialized in Digital System

Design: programing IC Chips

Southern Methodist University

May 2007

Dallas, Texas

2 of 2